entrepreneurship.org 2008-06-12

# Entrepreneurship.org

Respecting the privacy of the visitors using our Web sites is a major priority for the Ewing Marion Kauffman Foundation (the “Foundation ”). The following statement will help you understand how the Foundation collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our Web sites.

Please note that this policy applies only to the Foundation’s Web sites and not to any other organizations' Web sites to which we link. Remember that when you use a link to go from a Foundation Web site to another Web site, the Foundation’s Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites the Foundation links to, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read those rules and policies before proceeding. The Foundation does not make any representations about the practices and policies of any organization or Web site we link to and disclaims any liability or responsibility for such other Web site’s content, rules, policies or otherwise.

## Types of information we collect

The two types of information collected on any of the Foundation’s Web sites are: (1) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis (voluntary registration) and (2) Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.  
Voluntary Registration

Visitors to any of the Foundation’s Web sites may knowingly choose to register for any of the free e-mail newsletter(s). Visitors to Kauffman.org may knowingly choose to register for the “Thoughtbook.” Visitors interested in the Thoughtbook or any of the free e-email newsletters will be asked to voluntarily provide their name, e-mail address, telephone number, work address and other pertinent information. Visitors may also indicate topics of interest, which will assist us in tailoring our content to your needs.

You may have your name removed from any of our e-mailing lists at any time, by sending an e-mail to [kauffman@fulfillment-kc.com](mailto:kauffman@fulfillment-kc.com) with your name, e-mail address, and the words UNSUBSCRIBE in the 'subject' field.

## Cookies

To enable us to offer you the best possible experience when you visit the Foundation’s Web sites and to offer continually updated information, we assign you a unique identification number stored in a file on your computer called a "cookie." Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. This unique identification number automatically identifies your browser - but not you - to our computers whenever you interact and browse a Foundation Web site.

The cookies automatically gather certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Foundation’s Web Sites and areas visited on the sites. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to ensure that it is appealing to as many people possible.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

The Foundation does not rent, sell, or share any personal information collected through voluntary registration for the Kauffman Thoughtbook, free e-mail newsletters, or the "Contact Us" page -- except to provide the products or services you've requested.  
The information you provide to the Foundation is also used to better understand the content needs of registrants to our Web site. Our goal in collecting personal information through and monitoring visitor traffic patterns through use of cookies is to provide you with the best available Web experience for online entrepreneurship information.

THE FOUNDATION DOES NOT SHARE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ABOUT INDIVIDUAL USERS WITH ANY THIRD PARTY EXCEPT AS NECESSSARY FOR THE FOUNDATION TO OPERATE THE SITE AND COLLECT SUCH INFORMATION.

## Credit Card Information

If you choose to purchase products from the Foundation’s Web site <http://kauffman.org/eVenturing> or from any of the Foundation’s partners, you may need to provide personal information and authorization for us to obtain information from various credit services. For example, in addition to the information above, you may need to provide the following:

Mailing address Billing address Credit card number Telephone number

## Security

When personal information is provided to any of the Foundation’s Web sites, we require that you establish a "secure session" using Secure Socket Layer (SSL), or Secure Electronics Transaction (SET) protocol. The protocol encrypts all information before it is sent. The information is scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches our Web site.

Other e-mail communications may not be secure unless you are advised that security measures will be in place prior to you transmitting the information. For this reason, you should not send confidential information, such as Social Security number, through an unsecured e-mail.

## Your Consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by the Foundation as outlined in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page so that you always have the opportunity to be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
